Narrator: 28
Speaker: an accountant
Narrator: 26
Speaker: an actor
Narrator: 2
Speaker: an administrator
Narrator: 14
Speaker: an architect
Narrator: 6
Speaker: a builder
Narrator: 7
Speaker: a chef
Narrator: 27
Speaker: a cleaner
Narrator: 4
Speaker: a dentist
Narrator: 17
Speaker: a doctor
Narrator: 8
Speaker: an engineer
Narrator: 11
Speaker: a factory worker
Narrator: 22
Speaker: a flight attendant
Narrator: 13
Speaker: a footballer
Narrator: 30
Speaker: a guide
Narrator: 19
Speaker: a hairdresser
Narrator: 10
Speaker: a journalist
Narrator: 12
Speaker: a lawyer
Narrator: 1
Speaker: a manager
Narrator: 16
Speaker: a model
Narrator: 18
Speaker: a musician
Narrator: 5
Speaker: a nurse
Narrator: 21
Speaker: a pilot
Narrator: 23
Speaker: a police officer
Narrator: 24
Speaker: a receptionist
Narrator: 15
Speaker: a shop assistant
Narrator: 9
Speaker: a soldier
Narrator: 29
Speaker: a taxi driver
Narrator: 25
Speaker: a teacher
Narrator: 3
Speaker: a vet
Narrator: 20
Speaker: a waiter